#### Contact

vholt23@msn.com

www.linkedin.com/in/vanessa-holt-4694a914 (LinkedIn)

#### Top Skills

BLS

Medical/Surgical

Nursing

# Vanessa Holt

RN, BSN

Athens, Georgia Area

### Summary

Experienced Medical-Surgical/Telemetry RN with a demonstrated history of working in events and the higher education industry. Skilled in Patient Advocacy, Nursing Education, Medical-Surgical, Medication Administration, Telemetry, and Patient Education. Strong operations professional with a BSN from Brenau University.

#### Experience

Athens, GA

Travel RN
Travel RN
January 2017 - Present (3 years 6 months)

University of Georgia 23 years 5 months Athletic Department Event Staff 2004 - Present (16 years)

Coordinator for Student Services, Distance Education February 1997 - July 2009 (12 years 6 months) Athens, Georgia

Piedmont Athens Regional Staff RN January 2015 - January 2017 (2 years 1 month)

PruittHealth
Unit Manager
February 2014 - January 2015 (1 year)
Athens, GA

Ty Cobb Regional Medical Center RN, BSN January 2012 - January 2014 (2 years 1 month)

Page 1 of 2

Lavonia, GA

Gaines School Animal Hospital Veterinary Assistant 1995 - 1997 (2 years) Athens, GA

## Education

Brenau University
BSN, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2008 - 2011)

The University of Georgia

Bachelor of Arts (B.A.), Art History, Criticism and Conservation · (1985 - 1990)